Guide to the Rice News photo files, 1995-2006 UA 357
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: 2000-2006, 207065
  - Subseries C: 2002, 207136
    - December 5, 2002, 207170 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Photographs include: the Shepherd School Wind/Piano Quintet, Chris Shelburne, Jennifer Driskill, Meagan Walker, Erin Irvine, Jitka Frankova, Gordon Quan, Rice Philharmonics, Courtney Dow, Emily Matuzek, Andrew Engroff, and Spontaneous Combustion.
    - December 12, 2002, 207171 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Zenaido Camacho, Malcolm Gillis, and the finals study break.
  - Subseries D: 2003, 207172
    - January 16, 2003, 207173 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Photographs include: demolition of Old Wiess College, Kathleen Matthews, Robert Curl, and Nexus.
    - January 23, 2003, 207174 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Photographs include: Andrew Barron and Kathleen Matthews.
    - January 30, 2003, 207175 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Photographs and CD include: maps of Rice's building plans, Martin Luther King Jr candlelight vigil, Black Student Association, Jonathan Chism, Lani Guinier, and Malcolm Gillis.
    - February 6, 2003, 207176 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Photographs include: new Brown College commons.
    - February 13, 2003, 207177 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      Photographs include: Jan Odegard, Rice Terascale Cluster, and Stephen Gray.
    - February 20, 2003, 207178 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Photographs include: James Gaffigan, the Women's Resource Center seventh anniversary, Impact Awards, Rob Lentz, Crystal Su, Jessica Pena, Sarah Cloots, Nydia Mendoza, Elizabeth Pienkos, Raj Wahi, and Heather Masden.
    - February 27, 2003, 207179 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      Photographs include: Richard Smalley.
    - March 6, 2003, 207180 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - March 20, 2003, 207181 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Photographs include: Rice's Shell Center for Sustainability inaugural conference, Malcolm Gillis, Sir Philip Watts, Paula Dobriansky, Guy Hascoet, and Arthur Danto.
    - March 27, 2003, 207182 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Photographs include: Guillermo Fays, and Springfest.
    - April 3, 2003, 207183 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - April 10, 2003, 207184 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Photographs include: spring azaleas, Eve Bower, and Locks of Love.
    - April 17, 2003, 207185 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Photographs include: Fred Thompson, and the 50th anniversary of the Rice Associates Society.
    - April 24, 2003, 207186 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Photographs include: Ben Fonbuena, RiceFest, and Jenny Usakovsky.
    - May 1, 2003, 207187 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Photographs include: Steven L. Miller, James A. Baker III, Malcolm Gillis, Bill Broyles, and Andy Icken.
    - May 8, 2003, 207188 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Photographs include: Mikki Hebl.
    - May 29, 2003, 207189 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Photographs and CD include: Erin Mann, Malcolm Gillis, Terry Koonce, William Barnett, James Elkins, James Crownover, William Sick, Steven Miller, and ExxonMobile.
    - June 26, 2003, 207190 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Photographs include: Marty Merritt, the Science Academy of South Texas summer internship, Sandra Bulick, Kelly Bates, Pete Martinez, and Sandra Veliz.
    - July 31, 2003, 207191 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - August 28, 2003, 207192 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - September 4, 2003, 207193 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - September 11, 2003, 207194 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      Photographs include: Ken Nipe, Rape Aggression Defense, Lilly Bonner, Rick Schroder, Susan Hodge, and Malcolm Gillis.
    - September 18, 2003, 207195 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      Photographs include: observation of 9/11, the Rice Chorale, and Thomas Jaber.
    - September 25, 2003, 207196 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - October 2, 2003, 207197 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      Photographs include: Joe Arevalo, and Leonel Rivera.
    - October 9, 2003, 207198 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      Photographs include: Helmut Kohl, Susan Baker, James A. Baker III, the Berlin Wall, Malcolm Gillis, and the Rice observatory.
    - October 16, 2003, 207199 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      Photographs and CD include: Linda Ellerbee, Naomi Halas, and Jennifer West.
    - October 23, 2003, 207200 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      Photographs include: Kim Davenport, and "Ephemeral city: Cite Looks at Houston" essay cover.
    - October 30, 2003, 207201 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - November 6, 2003, 207202 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - November 13, 2003, 207203 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      Photographs include: Olusegun Obasanjo, and the Baker Institute for Public Policy.
    - November 20, 2003, 207204 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      Photographs and slides include: Amartya Sen, Richard Smalley, Robert Curl, and a Rice Owls football fan.
    - December 4, 2003, 207205 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Photographs, CD, and negatives include: Will Conrad, the academic quad, Jane Callan, Zenaido Camacho, the Holiday Bazaar, Jim Von Ehr, Robert Curl, and Richard Smalley.
    - December 11, 2003, 207206 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Photographs include: International Education Week,and Harriet Fulbright.
  - Subseries E: 2004, 207207
    - January 12, 2004, 207208 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - January 15, 2004, 207209 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - January 22, 2004, 207210 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - January 29, 2004, 207211 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      Photographs include: tree house in the quad, and Nyameko Barney Pityana.
    - February 5, 2004, 207212 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Photographs include: the Marching Owl Band in MTV's "Rock'N Jock Super Bowl XXXVIII", Leira Moreno, Hilda Rich, Hershel Rich, Malcolm Gillis, and the opening of the new Health and Wellness Center.
    - February 12, 2004, 207213 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Photographs include: Malcolm Gillis, Lessie Celestine, and Asa Hutchinson.
    - February 19, 2004, 207214 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Photographs include: David Leebron, Malcolm Gillis, Norman Hackerman, and George Will.
    - February 26, 2004, 207215 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Robert Samuelson.
    - March 11, 2004, 207216 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - March 18, 2004, 207217 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Photographs include: Noorain Khan.
    - March 25, 2004, 207218 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - April 1, 2004, 207219 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - April 15, 2004, 207220 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - April 22, 2004, 207221 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      Photographs include: James A. Baker III, Hosni Mubarak, and Edward Djerejian.
    - April 29, 2004, 207222 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Photographs include: Malcolm Gillis, Elizabeth Gillis, William Barnett, Milton Boniuk, Carol Quillen, and Anders Fogh Rasmussen.
    - May 6, 2004, 207223 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      Photographs include: Joel Wolfe, Elizabeth Long, Brian Gibson, James Brown, and Lynne Huffer.
    - May 27, 2004, 207224 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - June 30, 2004 (CD), 207225 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      Photographs include: Tom Lytle, and electric trains.
    - July 29, 2004, 207226 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - August 26, 2004, 207227 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - September 2, 2004 (CD), 207228 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - September 9, 2004, 207229 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - September 16, 2004, 207230 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - September 23, 2004, 207231 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - September 30, 2004, 207232 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - October 7, 2004 (CD), 207233 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - October 14, 2004, 207234 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      Photographs include: Rudy Giulani, and James A. Baker III.
    - October 21, 2004, 207235 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - October 28, 2004, 207236 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - November 4, 2004, 207237 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - November 11, 2004, 207238 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - November 18, 2004, 207239 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - December 2, 2004, 207240 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - December 9, 2004, 207241 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - December 16, 2004, 207242 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Subseries F: 2005, 207243
    - January 13, 2005, 207244 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - January 20, 2005, 207245 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - January 27, 2005, 207246 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - February 3, 2005, 207247 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - February 10, 2005, 207248 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - February 24, 2005, 207249 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - March 3, 2005, 207250 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - March 17, 2005 (CD), 207251 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - March 24, 2005, 207252 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - April 7, 2005, 207253 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - April 14, 2005 (CD), 207254 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - April 21, 2005, 207255 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - April 28, 2005 (CD), 207256 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - May 5, 2005, 207257 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - May 12, 2005, 207258 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - May 26, 2005, 207259 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - June 30, 2005 (CD), 207260 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - July 28, 2005 (CD), 207261 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - August 25, 2005 (CD), 207262 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - September 1, 2005 (CD), 207263 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - September 8, 2005 (CD), 207264 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - September 15, 2005 (CD), 207265 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - September 22, 2005 (CD), 207266 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - September 29, 2005, 207267 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - October 6, 2005 (CD), 207268 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - October 13, 2005 (CD), 207269 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - October 20, 2005 (CD), 207270 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - October 27, 2005 (CD), 207271 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - November 3, 2005 (CD), 207272 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - November 10, 2005 (CD), 207273 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - November 17, 2005 (CD), 207274 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - December 1, 2005 (CD), 207275 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - December 8, 2005 (CD), 207276 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - December 15, 2005 (CD), 207277 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Subseries G: 2006, 207278
    - January 12, 2006 (CD), 207279 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - January 19, 2006 (CD), 207280 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - January 26, 2006 (CD), 207281 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - February 2, 2006 (CD), 207282 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - February 9, 2006 (CD), 207283 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - February 16, 2006 (CD), 207284 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - February 23, 2006 (CD), 207285 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - March 2, 2006, 207286 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - March 9, 2006 (CD), 207287 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - March 23, 2006 (CD), 207288 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - March 30, 2006 (CD), 207289 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - April 6, 2006 (CD), 207290 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - April 13, 2006 (CD), 207291 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - April 20, 2006 (CD), 207292 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - April 27, 2006 (CD), 207293 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - May 4, 2006 (CD), 207294 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - May 11, 2006, 207295 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - May 25, 2006 (CD), 207296 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - June 29, 2006 (CD), 207297 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - July 27, 2006 (CD), 207298 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - August 17, 2006, 207299 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - August 24, 2006 (CD), 207300 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - August 31, 2006, 207301 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - September 7, 2006, 207302 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - September 14, 2006, 207303 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - September 21, 2006, 207304 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - September 28, 2006, 207305 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - October 5, 2006, 207306 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - October 12, 2006, 207307 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - October 19, 2006, 207308 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - October 26, 2006 (CD), 207309 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - November 2, 2006, 207310 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - November 9, 2006 (CD), 207311 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - November 16, 2006, 207312 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - November 30, 2006, 207313 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - December 7, 2006 (CD), 207314 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - December 14, 2006 (CD), 207315 (Box 22, Folder 34)